Like Mike 2: Streetball is a family, comedy,
fantasy film directed by David Nelson.
Another young boy with 'hoop dreams' finds an old pair of Michael Jordan's sneakers
and can suddenly play ball like the greatest player in the world.
Jerome, played by Jascha Washington.
Ray, played by Kel Mitchell.
Senior, played by Michael Beach.
Rodney, played by Brett Kelly.
Nathan, played by Micah Williams.
KOTC Announcer, played by Clyde Drexler.
Like Mike 2: Streetball (simply titled Like Mike 2 in various regions) is a
2006 American sports comedy film directed by David Nelson.
Contrary to the film title, it is not a plot continuation of the 2002
film nor does it feature any of the original cast members.
The film explores themes of sports, basketball, sreetball.
The tone is lighthearted.